clamwin.com 2012-06-22

# Our Privacy Statement

ClamWin Pty. Ltd. Is firmly committed to protecting your privacy. To clarify our position on privacy, we have created this privacy statement to disclose the information gathering and dissemination practices for our Web Site: ClamWin.com. 

Personal information collected on this website will only be used for the purposes stated at the time of collection. Your personal information will not be added to a mailing list or used for any other purpose without your consent.

**Information Automatically Logged**  
Our Web Site collects non-personally identifiable information, for example, browser type, operating system, domain name, time spent on the Web Site, or referring link. This information may be used for system, Web Site, and process improvements. We do not transfer or sell this information to anyone or any organization. 

**Cookies**  
We use "cookies" to help us identify and track your usage and navigation of our Web Site. These "cookies" are small text files that contain a unique identification number and do not contain any personally identifying information. The cookie is transferred from our Web Site to your computer's memory or disk. However, when you close your browser, the information stored in this "cookie" and ceases to be available to us. If, after this explanation of "cookies" and our use of them, you are still uncomfortable with them, you can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, allowing you to decide whether to accept it or block it. If you block the "cookie", you may still use our site (although functionality may be limited in certain situations). 

**Registration Forms**  
You may use a "Contact Us" form on our Web Site to submit a personal message. The form asks for the users name and e-mail address. This is information is used to reply to the user. The e-mail addresses submitted via the "Contact Us" form are not shared or sold to anyone. 

**Mailing Lists**  
Our site maintains a mailing list by use of SourceForge.net mailman service. Please see [SourceForge.net Privacy Statement](http://sourceforge.net/tos/privacy.php). We will not add users to our mailing list against the consent of our users. Only users can subscribe themselves. When subscribing, they will be sent a confirmation e-mail, asking them to reply to the confirmation.  
Once subscribed, users can remove themselves from receiving future mailings. 

**External Links**  
Our Web Site contains links to other sites. ClamWin Pty. Ltd. is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites. This privacy statement applies solely and exclusively to the information collected at our Web Site. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our Web Site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects any information from you that is personally identifiable. 

**Special Relationships**  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please visit the following links: 

  * Google Adsense. See the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)
  * Digital River. To find out more about how Digital River manages the privacy and security of information for customer orders, please see the [Digital River Privacy Policy](http://www.digitalriver.com/corporate/privacy.shtml).

**Donations**  
Our Web Site accepts donations via PayPal.com web site. Please see [PayPal Privacy Statement](http://www.paypal.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=p/gen/ua/policy_privacy-outside).  
  
© 2012 ClamWin Free Antivirus  
ClamWin™ is a trademark of ClamWin Pty Ltd.  
Other trademarks are the property of the respective trademark holders.
